<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Econ-CS Learning Blog</title>
  
  
  <link href="https://shoal-rat.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="https://shoal-rat.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2024-01-15T12:47:27.386Z</updated>
  <id>https://shoal-rat.github.io/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>Shoal Rat</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="https://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>考试顺利呀</title>
    <link href="https://shoal-rat.github.io/2024/01/15/%E8%80%83%E8%AF%95%E9%A1%BA%E5%88%A9%E5%91%80/"/>
    <id>https://shoal-rat.github.io/2024/01/15/%E8%80%83%E8%AF%95%E9%A1%BA%E5%88%A9%E5%91%80/</id>
    <published>2024-01-15T12:47:05.000Z</published>
    <updated>2024-01-15T12:47:27.386Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>祝你成功❤</p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;祝你成功❤&lt;/p&gt;
</summary>
      
    
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>How to build a blog by yourself-Part 1 Github</title>
    <link href="https://shoal-rat.github.io/2024/01/15/blog-building/"/>
    <id>https://shoal-rat.github.io/2024/01/15/blog-building/</id>
    <published>2024-01-15T12:27:24.000Z</published>
    <updated>2024-01-15T12:46:25.172Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>If you hope to build a blog by yourself, you can first register a account in GitHub. Attention, you may need some tools which have magic to let you bypass some walls in somewhere, and you can reach <a href="https://github.com/">GitHub</a>.</p><p>After you intered into github, you can first go into your profile, which named <a href="https://github.com/[your">https://github.com/[your</a> github name] as for me, my github profile is <a href="https://github.com/shoal-rat">https://github.com/shoal-rat</a>. And what’s next? You should click repositories on the left side of your screen. Then click a green botton named “New”. And this step is importent, the Repository name must be named “[your name].github.io”, such as “shoal-rat.github.io”. You can choose add a readme doc up to you. </p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;If you hope to build a blog by yourself, you can first register a account in GitHub. Attention, you may need some tools which have magic </summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="Computer Science" scheme="https://shoal-rat.github.io/categories/Computer-Science/"/>
    
    
    <category term="Blog" scheme="https://shoal-rat.github.io/tags/Blog/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Introduction of my GPTs</title>
    <link href="https://shoal-rat.github.io/2024/01/12/GPTs/"/>
    <id>https://shoal-rat.github.io/2024/01/12/GPTs/</id>
    <published>2024-01-12T09:56:12.000Z</published>
    <updated>2024-01-15T12:24:18.640Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>First and foremost, the most powerful GPT is my personal statement generate GPT, I used it to refine most of my personal statement, and it can also take you to do some brainstorming, and find your spark places in the personal statement, I uploaded the main use methods under this GPT so you can direct ask questions about how to use it. You can questions, such as: </p><p>1.When interacting with the Personal Statement Generator GPT, consider exploring these avenues:</p><p>Prompt-Driven Refinement: Ask for the top ten most effective prompts designed to elevate the quality of your personal statement. These prompts are tailored to draw upon a comprehensive range of knowledge, ensuring a nuanced and impactful refinement of your content.</p><p>Expert-Led Brainstorming: Leverage the GPT’s expertise for a deep brainstorming session. The focus here is threefold: to identify your unique features, crystallize your future aspirations, and pinpoint past experiences that can be strategically woven into your personal statement or motivation letter. This process is not just about drafting a document; it’s about discovering and articulating the essence of your individual journey and ambitions.</p><p>2.How to Engage with the GPT</p><p>To make the most of this resource, simply pose your questions or requests directly. For instance, you might ask:</p><p>a. What are the ten most efficient prompts for enhancing my personal statement?<br>b. Can you assist me in brainstorming to identify my unique characteristics, future goals, and relevant past experiences for my personal statement?</p><p>This approach ensures a tailored and focused enhancement of your personal statement, making it not only a reflection of your achievements but also a testament to your aspirations and individuality.</p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;First and foremost, the most powerful GPT is my personal statement generate GPT, I used it to refine most of my personal statement, and i</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="GPT" scheme="https://shoal-rat.github.io/categories/GPT/"/>
    
    
    <category term="AIGC" scheme="https://shoal-rat.github.io/tags/AIGC/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
